ARTIST'S STATEMENT

We have the prettiest house in the land but don't scratch the clap boards or you will expose the rot. Don't look in the mirror for you may see the hopeless beggar on their way to the gallows of spiraling debt and unreliable employment. Don't think about that for surely the problems lies in exposed skin, interlocking body parts and unaffordable gestatation.

These pictures represent interpretations from the last 25 years. They are a rejection of the unquestioning cult of empty positivity in our society. They represent disappointment that the propaganda was not true and what I was drinking had a very bad after-taste.

I have taken bits from from Goya, Vonnegut, New Objectivity, comics and cartoons; cut them up and shuffled them around into a mish-mash of junk and then tried to assemble it into a beautiful blackness.

Thank you,
Anthony Baker
portfolio.deluxeluxury.com/#artwork

ANTHONY BAKER

WORK EXPERIENCE

ATLANTA, GA THE MORRISON AGENCY Senior Web Developer 2015

U1 DESIGN/HOTHOUSE INC. ATLANTA, GA Senior Designer/Developer 2005 to 2015

DELUXE LUXURY DESIGN MONTREAL, QC Freelancer 2001 to 2005

MYBUTLER.COM MONTREAL, QC 1998 to 2001 Senior Designer

STILL CURRENT DESIGN ATLANTA, GA Designer 1991 to 1998

SOFTWARE EXPERIENCE

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE

Edge Animator, Illustrator, Photoshop Extended, InDesign, Flash, Dreamweaver, After Effects and SoundBooth

MICROSOFT OFFICE

Word, Powerpoint and Excel

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

UNIVERSITY OF MONTREAL 2003 TO 2004

Internet Programming

ART INSTITUTE OF ATLANTA 1989 TO 1991

Associates in Visual Communications

WEB SPACE

GITHUB PROFILE:

github.com/SuperFastCola

PORTFOLIO:

portfolio.deluxeluxury.com portfolio.deluxeluxury.com/#artwork portfolio.deluxeluxury.com/#illos

PROGRAMMING EXPERIENCE

PHP/MYSQL:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/timezonehandler/blob/master/ TimeZoneHandler php

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/autodeploy/blob/master/ DeployHandler.php

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/db_connection_class

NODEJS:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/nodeplay

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/node-site/blob/master/app.js

JAVASCRIPT AND JQUERY:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/MusicManager

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/video/blob/master/video.js https://github.com/SuperFastCola/Browser.js/blob/master/browser.js

HTML 5 CANVAS GAME DEVELOPMENT:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/Ball-Thrower-Game-Code

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/reactjs-project/blob/master/app/ components/main.js

ANGULAR.JS:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/dld_site/blob/angular/javascript/ src/dld.v2.js

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/dld_site/blob/angular/index.html

BACKBONE.JS:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/dld_site/blob/ master/javascript/new_dld_v1.js

CHEF AND AWS OPSWORKS:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/chefs_table

FACEBOOK API:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/facebook_processing_ajax/blob/ master/fb_ajax.phpl

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/reactjs-project/blob/master/app/ modules/styles.scss

BASH:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/bashing

WORDPRESS INTEGRATION:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/wordpress_theme_customization/ blob/master/functions.php

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/wordpress_theme_customization/ blob/master/index.php

OBJECTIVE-C:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/Superfastapp/blob/master/ SuperFastCola/SpringyView.m

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/Superfastapp/blob/master/ SuperFastCola/SuperSoundPlayer.m

DEPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

AWS LAMBDA/SNS/DYNAMO DB:

 $https://github.com/SuperFastCola/nodeplay/blob/master/sns_dynamo.js$

AWS SIMPLE EMAIL SERVICE:

https://github.com/SuperFastCola/email-sender-amazon

OTHER AWS SERVICES:

S3. EC2. Route 53. Elastic Beanstalk. RDS